# **ISAAC WEISS**

Auburn, AL (334) 748-1379 weissic@icloud.com

isaacweiss.dev github.com/icweiss22 linkedin.com/in/icweiss22

### **SKILLS**

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ¡Query, knockout.js, DataTables, AJAX
- Languages: C#, C++, Java, Python, Swift, SQL
- Tools: .NET ecosystem, Visual Studio, VS Code, **SSMS**
- Collaboration: GitHub. Teams, Jira, Service Now
- Other: Entity Framework, LINQ, Razor

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Auburn University**

Samuel Ginn College of Engineering Auburn, AL Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, Business Concentration

Minor: French August 2019 - December 2023

GPA: 3.97/4.00

Member of the Dean's List (>3.8 GPA) Every Semester Awarded Spirit of Auburn Presidential Scholarship – Full Tuition for students with 34 score on ACT (SAT 1500) Awarded ADTRAN Scholarship (\$1000) for outstanding students in Computer Science French Club Treasurer

References Upon Request

#### **SUMMARY**

Auburn University senior majoring in Computer Science with a Business concentration and a French minor. Very passionate about software engineering, with experience in web development using the .NET ecosystem. Familiar with back-end (SSMS, SQL), middleware (.NET, C#), and front-end (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) tools.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Campus Web Solutions Auburn, AL (May 2021 – December 2022) Full-stack co-op at a web development firm specializing in developing robust web applications for Auburn University.

- Designed, developed, and maintained 30+ of Auburn University's most used web applications using strict coding regulations and security practices, including AU's Vaccine and Pharmacy Scheduler, AU's Board of Trustees Voting System, and AU's Event Ticketing System.
- Leveraged an array of web development tools including HTML, CSS, .NET Framework, ¡Query, C#, Visual Studio, and SSMS to create dynamic and robust digital solutions.
- Assumed mentorship role, providing hands-on learning, conducting live practice sessions, and authoring a comprehensive web development guide to nurture and guide newer co-ops.
- Actively participated in client meetings, effectively communicating technical concepts, and proposing innovative ideas that garnered client approval.
- Implemented agile development methodologies to streamline project workflows, tracking and managing 100+ deliverables with precision using Jira, resulting in timely project completions.
- Prioritized mobile responsiveness, crafting applications that seamlessly adapt across diverse devices. Conducted comprehensive runtime analyses and eliminating performance bottlenecks.
- Led the end-to-end redesign and development initiative for the Auburn University Vice President of Research's site pages (cws.auburn.edu/ovpr), creating a dynamic backend system empowering the client to effortlessly update and manage content.

Exchange Student, Toulon, France (January 2023 – June 2023)

Immersed deeply in the local culture while honing language proficiency. Committed to intensive language learning and fostering cross-cultural understanding, contributing to a rich and diverse global perspective.

Hackathon Logistics Coordinator, Auburn, AL (September 2019 – February 2020) Successfully managed scheduling, room assignments, vendor communication, and more for months leading up to the event. During the event, ensured seamless execution of tasks such as coordinating food services and providing real-time support to participants, contributing to the success of a memorable and impactful Hackathon.

Front Service Clerk, *Publix* Auburn, AL (June 2018 – October 2020)

Efficiently processed customer transactions as cashier and bagger while maintaining a friendly and approachable demeanor, contributing to a positive brand image.